<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Bell pepper</string>

    <string name="Powdery_Mildew_recommendation"> Pepper leaf curl regularly appears on hot days, during the middle of summer; hot winds combined with low humidity cause leaves to cup in self-defense. If leaves curl only in response to heat try adding extra water during the middle of the day to keep the plants tissues cooler.
Water much less and keep the substrate on the "dry-side". Obviously don\'t cause them to become dehydrated, but significantly reduce watering.Reduce humidity levels. There are mutliple ways to do this, but the easiet way is. Increase air flow. Increased airflow is all round beneficial to plants and infact the plants should be swaying slightly if grown indoors.
</string>
    <string name="Leaf_Curl_Virus_recommendation"> Powdery mildew on pepper can be difficult. The white powdery growth characteristic of powdery mildew diseases occurs only on the underside of leavesand it will turn brown rather than remaining white. Diffuse yellow spotting often develops on the upper surface. Affected leaves tend to drop off the plant, as occurs with bacterial leaf spot.
Baking soda is one of the best home remedies for treating powdery mildew. For this method, 1ix 1 tablespoon baking soda and ½ teaspoon liquid soap in 1 gallon of water. Transfer it into a spray bottle and spray the tops and underside of leaves and any other affected areas. Although this works best as a preventative measure, it\’s also known to be effective on existing powdery mildew infections as well.
</string>
    <string name="Yellow_Leaves_recommendation">Pepper Plant Leaves are Yellow Due to a Lack of Water and Nutrients. One of the two most common reasons for yellow leaves on a pepper plant is either under watering or a lack of nutrients in the soil.
The chlorine in the water can cause the leaves to turn yellow and eventually die. To fix this problem, you will need to start watering your pepper plants with filtered or distilled water. This will help to remove the chlorine from the water and protect your pepper plants.
</string>
</resources>